[Music]
hello hello is anybody home
it's my Andy it's 3 p.m.
I'm here to sell my balls you know just
like we arranged in the walnut parking
lot
[Music]
open the [ __ ] door [ __ ] I know
you're in there come on we got to do
this before my boyfriend man and gets
home he's at McDonald's right now eating
a happy meal so open up already hey if
you open up I might just let you [ __ ] me
in the ass
[Music]
open the [ __ ] door [ __ ] I'm not
playing games here listen I don't care
that you're only seven years old I need
the money and you said you would give me
four dollars if I was out she was
did you really lock the [ __ ] door you
think that will stop me I'm of a gang
[ __ ] [ __ ] a damn lock won't stop me
what the [ __ ] did you [ __ ] call the
cops on the [ __ ] I'll [ __ ] kill you
we have you surrounded
lay down your weapons and come out with
your hand you son of a [ __ ] you just
signed your own death warrant the only
one getting out of here alive
I always carry a gun
in my book that